银湖动物救助中心
SILVERLAKE ANIMAL RESCUE
就这个
That one.
乖孩子
Here boy.
你很重耶
You're heavy.
还爱流口水
And slobbery.
戴上
There.
你是个好孩子
You're a good boy!
我的好孩子
You're my good boy!
5年之后
5 YEARS LATER
喂!
Hello!
宝贝 我时间不多
Honey, I don't have much time!
爸爸?
Daddy?
你还好么?
Are you okay?
工作上出了些事情 宝贝
Something came up at work, honey.
爸爸这段时间不能回家了
Daddy is not gonna be home for a while.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你也不能再回家里去 知道了么 Penny
You can't go back to the house, Penny. Okay?
发生什么事了?
What's happening?
没事的 你不会孤单的
It's allright. You won't be alone.
有Bolt陪你
You have Bolt.
我改造了他
I've altered him.
他现在能保护你了
He can protect you now.
片 名 : 闪 电 狗
谢谢 这可真是个好消息
Thank you. Which that of course is wonderful news.
一切都已经就位
Everything is positioning nicely.
就是他 卡利科博士!
There he is, doctor Calico!
有没有运气能激发我们客人的勇气?
Any luck getting our guest to spill his guts?
噢 会激发出他的勇气来的
Oh, his guts will spill.
看用什么办法了
One way or another.
不 我绝不会说的
Never, I'll never talk.
爸爸!
Daddy!
你是在激怒我 教授 我很生气
You're beginning to urge me profesor, I'm urged.
但这无济于事 一旦包裹到达...
And that will not do. As the package arrived...
我想我们亲爱的朋友 会更容易沟通...
...I think it might make our dear friend a bit more communicative.
我正派人去把它取来
I'm sending an agent to pick it up.
太好了 让他做头班飞机带给我
Gorgeous! Have him bring it to me on the first flight.
Bolt 出发!
Bolt, let's go!
我们只要那女孩!
We only need the girl!
- 什么? - 卡利科在哪?
- What? - Where is Calico?
我才不会告诉你呢
I'm not talking to you.
玻利维亚 玻利维亚 卡利科在玻利维亚!
Bolivia, Bolivia, Calico is in Bolivia!
靠近罗加瓜多湖
Near lake Rogaguado!
罗加瓜多湖? 我早该想到的
Lake Rogaguado? I should have known!
来吧 Bolt 我们走
Come on Bolt, let's go.
玻利维亚 10分钟后有一班飞机去那儿
Bolivia, there is a flight leaving in 10 minutes.
Bolt 急速移动!
Bolt, zoom zoom!
Bolt 去取回来
Bolt, prinde.
小狗狗!
Puppy!
锁定
LOCK
好样的!
Good boy!
去机场!
Airport!
Bolt 狮子吼
Bolt, speak.
好了
Okay, okay...
干得漂亮 伙计
Good job, buddy.
任务完成!
Mission accomplished!
那是个守卫
That's a keeper!
没事了 硬汉 你把他们都抓住了
It's allright tough guy, you caught them all.
没事啦 Bolt 你又一次拯救了世界
Don't worry Bolt, you've saved the day again.
好孩子!
Good boy!
去机场!
Airport!
Bolt 狮子吼
Bolt, speak.
麦克风吊杆!
Boom mike!
- 有一个传声器架 - 是个传声器架
- We got a boom mike. - That's a boom mike.
真糟糕
That's sloppy.
狗会看见这个的 他可能已经看见了!
The dog could've seen that. He could've seen that!
就算是狗看到了又怎样?
Uh, who cares if the dog sees a boom mike?
请允许我先问一句...
Forgive me for answering a question with a question,...
你又是谁?
...but who are you?
联播网的明迪・帕克
Mindy Parker, from the network.
当然 我来问你 联播网的明迪・帕克
Of course. Let me ask you, Mindy from the network...
你从这里看到了什么?
What do you see here?
- 呃 小狗? - 她说"小狗"
- Uhh... the dog? - "The dog" she says.
噢 明迪 可怜的明迪
Oh, Mindy. Poor, poor Mindy.
我说错什么了么?
Am I missing something?
你大错特错了 明迪
You're missing everything, Mindy.
你看见的是一只狗 我看见的是这样一个动物
You see a dog. I see an animal that believes...
他全心全意相信
...with every fiber of his being, every fiber...
他爱的女孩处在最危险的关头
...that the girl he loves is in mortal danger.
狗的表情里流露出的深沉情感
I see a depth of emotion on the face of that canine the likes of which...
此前从未在荧幕上出现过
...has never been captured on screen before.
从未啊 联播网的明迪
Never, Mindy from the network.
我们就是要让他相信 这一切都是真实的
We jump through hoops to make sure Bolt believes everything is real.
这就是为什么 我们不用场记 不重拍
It's why we don't miss marks. It's why we don't reshoot.
这就是为什么我们绝不 让狗看到传声器架
And it's why we most certainly do not let the dog see boom mikes!
因为 联播网的明迪
Because, Mindy from the network,...
只有那狗相信...
...if the dog believes it,...
观众们才会相信
...the audience believes it.
好吧 你想要现实就给你现实
Wow. Okay, you want reality, here you go chief.
这个剧情太老套了
The show's too predictable.
女孩有危险 小狗从可怕的英国佬 手里救下她 我们都知道
The girl's in danger, the dog saves her from the creepy english guy, we get it.
总是个大团圆的结局
There's always a happy ending.
我们的调查小组称 18到35岁的成人并不满意
And our focus groups tell us 18 to 35 year olds are unhappy.
他们不喜欢皆大欢喜的结局
They're not happy with happy.
或许你可以...
So maybe you should, I don't know,...
少花点时间担心小狗的行动方式
...spend a little less time worrying about the dog's method acting,...
而多花点时间想想
...and more time figuring out how to stop 20 year olds in Topeka...
如何阻止20岁的人换频道
...from changing the channel.
要是收视率下降半个点...
Because if you lose so much as half a rating point,...
我发誓 把你们都炒了 就从你开始!
...so help me, I will fire everyone in this room, starting with you!
这个够现实吧
How's that for real?
贴这里 很好
There. Perfect.
你又一次救了我 Bolt
You saved me again, Bolt.
好了 没什么的
It's okay, it's nothing.
没有坏人了
No more bad guys.
你要吃东西么 你饿不饿?
Do you want some food, Bolty? Huh? Are you hungry?
你把他们都逮住了 Bolt 没人能伤害我了
You've got them, Bolt, no one is gonna hurt me.
Bolt 看看我 我没事的 看到没?
Bolt, look at me. I'm fine, see?
到这来 伙计 到这来!
Come here buddy, come here!
去 捡回来 Bolt 去呀
Go, get it Bolt! Go, get it!
这个也不好玩了
Yeah, that one is no funny either.
看哪 我们找到什么了?
Well, what we have here?
你的老朋友 胡萝卜先生!
Your old buddy, Mister Carrot!
噢 Bolt!
Oh, Bolt!
我得走了
You know I have to go.
真是我的好孩子
Yeah, you are my good boy.
在这里啊 我的超级明星
And there she is, my little superstar!
我们来为"青少年"杂志 拍张封面照吧
Let's get to that "Teen" vogue cover shoot.
妈妈 我想带Bolt回家度周末
Mam, I wanna take Bolt home for this weekend.
- 这个...我... - 噢 这很好
- Well, I... I'm... - Oh, that be nice. That be great.
会很不错的 小女孩和她的狗
That would. A little girl and her dog.
再好不过了
Nothing better that.
这么说 我能带Bolt回家了?
So I can bring Bolt home?
作为你的朋友 我会说是的 当然可以
As your friend, I say yes, absolutely...
但是作为你的经纪人 我得提醒你 对Bolt的规则是
...but as your agent, I have to remind you. This is Bolt's law.
他必须留在这里
He has to stay right here.
好了 我们走
Okay, let's go.
但他从没有过过真正的生活
But he never gets to be a real dog.
就一次 这周末带他回家
And it will be only for the weekend and I just once...
什么 知道吗 这问题很公平 这么着吧 比方说拿出来个别针
What? You know what? It's a fair question. Let's do this, let's put a pin in it.
别在这 这样就行了 现在让我们先放一放吧
Pin in, there you go. Now, let's let that hang there a little bit...
等想通了我们再来讨论 好么?
...and then we'll address that when we thought things through, okay?
大家觉得怎么样? 都笑一笑!
Good enough for everybody? Smiles all around!
我们走吧 快点
Let's get out of here. Come on.
我不想想那么多 我想带Bolt回家
I don't need to think it through. I wanna take Bolt home.
瞧瞧你可爱的小脸 我家里也有个小女儿
Look at this face! I have a little girl at home,...
我毕生的爱 我愿意为她做任何事
...love of my life. I would do anything for her.
但我还是会心跳不已地拿她和你换!
And I would trade her for you in a heartbeat!
真的
True story.
这提醒我 这就得重新做衣柜了
That reminds me, uh, we need to begin over to wardrobe.
我们走吧
Let's go.
- 我需要... - 我...我只是...
- I need every... - I... I just...
这么说 小狗认为这全都是真的?
So, the dog thinks this is all real?
是啊 新鲜吧 这家伙从没离开过片场
Oh, yeah. Hear new. Guy never leaves the set.
难以置信 等有机会 我就把这个公布出来
It's unbelievable. Whenever I get a chance this is the perfect way to unwind.
就用邪恶的大笑来开始
I like to start with an evil laugh.
嘿 小毛球!
Hello, hairballs!
或许今天你赢了 Bolt 但最终
You may have one today Bolt, but in the end...
我们还是会抓到你的小Penny
...we will get your little Penny.
不见得 小猫 既然你选择了邪恶之路
Not likely cat. For you've choosen to follow the path of evil,...
到头来我们会摧毁你 还有你邪恶的傀儡主人
...ultimately we'll destroy you, along with your fiendish puppet master.
- 喔! - 我知道 看看这个
- Wow! - I know. Okay, watch this.
她要完蛋了 小狗 绿眼人已经制定了计划
She is a goner, dog. But green-eyed man has a plan...
很快就会付诸实施的
...and soon he will execute it.
然后他会干掉她的!
Yeah and then he will execute her!
说的不错!
Nice!
我本可以用狮子吼来 让你们两个滚蛋
I would super bark you both back into the hole you crawled out of...
但我需要你活着
...but I need you alive...
因为我要你给绿眼人捎个信儿
...because I got a little message for you to take back to your green-eyed man.
告诉他 他的老朋友Bolt说他...
You tell him, his old friend Bolt said he...
这很长么?
Is it long?
- 什么长不长? - 要带的口信
- Is what long? - The message.
那口信很长么? 我的记性不好
Is it a long message? Because I have a horrible memory.
长话短说 好了吧 你告诉他说 我要...
Yeah, I'll make a brief, all right? You tell him I said, I'm gonna...
干脆我们这么着吧
You know what? Why don't we do this?
你来记前一半 我来记后面的部分
You remember the first half of the message and then I remember the second.
然后我们拼在一起 就可以把它带绿眼人了
And then we can pass it on green-eyed man together.
我不管你们怎么把话带到
I don't care how the message is translated, alright?
只要带到就行 告诉绿眼人 我不会轻易罢手的
Just do it, okay? Tell the green-eyed man, that I will not sleep,...
不将Penny救出来 我绝不善罢甘休
...I will not rest until my Penny is safe from his evil clutches.
你告诉绿眼人 我会...
You tell the green-eyed man, I'll...
字数太多了 像什么"什么?""呼?"...
Way too many words! I was like, "what?", and then I was like "huh?"...
还有什么"我有点无聊" 还有些跟爪子有关系?
...and then "I got a little bored". Some about clutches?
无论如何 我尽力吧 再见
Anyway, I'll do my best! Ciao!
顺便说 粉丝很多 都喜欢这个 喜欢你 得走了 谢谢
By the way, huge fan, love it, love you, gotta go. Thank you!
给我回来 你这坏蛋 讨厌又下贱
Get back here, you... You sick! Revolting, low some little...
狗啊!
Dogs!
猫啊!
Cats!
我绝不会让他们抓到你的 Penny!
I'll never let them get you, Penny!
准备好了么 Bolt?
You ready, Bolt?
三号摄影机 拉远
Let's widen out camera three.
四号准备 开始!
Ready four! Go four!
还有...司机
And... driver.
谢谢 拉里
Thanks, Larry.
脚踏车就位 栏杆准备好
Allright Scooter, right the grade. Ready on the propel bars.
跟上他们!
And track with them!
卡利科的超级电脑
Calico's super computer.
要是我们能侵入...
If we can access it...
就能知道他们把我爸爸关在哪里了
...we'll find and learn where they're keeping my father.
武器准备就绪热
The weapon is hot.
准备激光眼
"Heat vision" time.
Bolt 激光眼!
Bolt, stare!
快!
Now!
干得好
Nice move.
快点 快啊!
Come on, come on!
如此的牺牲精神 感动死我啦!
Such devotion... It brings tears to my eyes!
卡利科!
Calico!
你父亲的发现 对我们组织极为重要
Your father's discoveries could be a great use to our organization.
等我抓到了"幸运的Penny"后
I'm sure, he will be more commutating...
他会更加合作一些!
...now that I've got his "lucky Penny"!
Bolt!
世界将由我掌握!
World domination is waiting my grasp!
调查小组对这个结尾怎么看?
How did you focus groups feel about the end of this?
你要迎合18到35岁的观众群
You asked for unhappy 18 to 35 years old,...
我就给他们一个悲剧的结局
...I give you unhappy 18 to 35 year olds.
Bolt 没事的 Bolt 我很好
Bolt, it's okay Bolt. I'm fine.
守卫 拦住她
Guards, stop her!
- 嘿 嘿! - Bolt!
- Hey, hey! - Bolt!
- 停下来! - 听听他的叫声
- Hold on! - Listen to him.
- 他需要知道我没事 - 不 你有事
- He needs to know I'm okay. - No, you're not okay.
你已经被恶魔般的卡利科博士绑架
You've been kidnapped by fiendish Doctor Calico.
至少我们要那只小狗这么想...
At least that is what the dog needs to think but...
想一想吧 等他明天营救了你后
...just imagine, close your eyes and imagine how excited he'll be...
他该多兴奋
...when he saves you, tomorrow. OK?
但他整晚都会担心的 求你了 让我...
But he's gonna be freaking out all night. Please, just let me...
等一下 你耳朵后面是什么东西?
Wait a second. What's that behind your ear?
是个...对了 是个别针!
Is that a... Yes, it is! It's a pin!
这么着吧 先把这次谈话别起来
Let's do this. Let's take the pin and put it in this conversation.
但不是完全搁下不管 不是的 直到这件事情解决
And we will not take it down, no m'am, until this matter is resolved.
- 但我只是... - 我记得有件什么事来着?
- But I just... - What's that reminds me up?
DVD发售会赶紧出发吧 那可是很大的活动
The DVD release junket. Let's get going. It's a big push.
我想打扮时髦的去参加发售会
I want to go with a modern looks.
好了 给她点空间吧 别挤着我们的天才了
Allright, okay. Let's give her some air. Let's not crowd the talent.
我一直在练习这种邪恶的笑 有没有一种邪恶的笑
I've been working on my evil laugh. Is there an evil laugh like...
像这样的
With that.
好了 是这么回事 你还不会邪恶的笑
Okay, here is the thing. You're not ready for the evil laugh.
你可以在我邪恶笑之后 吃吃的轻笑几声
You could do a chuckle, like a mildly upset chuckle...
像是让人心烦的吃吃笑 听我的
...after my evil laugh. Listen to mine.
嘿 Bolt!
Hey Bolt!
他爬出来了!
Climbing here!
Bolt 回来!
Bolt, come back!
我来晚了
I'm too late.
- Bolt 救命! - 我来了 Penny!
- Bolt, help! - I'm coming Penny!
Bolt 救命!
Bolt, help!
坚持住 Penny 坚持住!
Hold on, Penny. Hold on!
Bolt 救命!
Bolt, help!
Penny!
Bolt 到这来 Bolt!
Bolt! Here, Bolt!
好了 Bolt 冷静! 你要冷静 Bolt!
Okay, Bolty, okay! Stay cool! You're cool, Bolty!
绿眼人!
The green-eyed man!
Penny! Penny!
Penny!
目标出现!
Target acquired!
到此为止吧!
It ends here!
Penny!
Penny! 她被转移走了
Penny! They moved her.
顾不上礼数了 兄弟
There is no time for formalities, brothers.
我主人处在危险中 我...
My person is in danger and I... I...
- 喔 你在干嘛! - 哦 对不起
- Wow! What're you doing? - Oh, I'm sorry.
- 你想先闻闻我么? - 什么?
- You wanna sniff mine first? - What?
- 你不是这片儿的 对吧? - 嘿 停下!
- Not from around here, are you? - Hey, stop it!
- 怎么了? - 这事很严肃
- What? - This is serious.
嘿 你在这里 你走丢了么 宝贝?
Hey, there. Are you lost sweety?
嘿 等等!
Hey, wait!
为什么我弄不弯这些讨厌的栏杆?
Why can't I bend these stupid bars?
噢 伙计
Oh, buddy!
你的头卡得还真是刚刚好啊
You got your head stucked pretty good, huh guy?
嘿 伙计们 到这了 看看这个 他的大头给卡住了
Hey guys, come here. Check this out! He's got his mellon stucked.
是呀 真是个傻大头
Yup, that is one stucked mellon.
嘿 嘿 伙计 放松 慢点
Hey, hey buddy, take it easy! Slow down.
我没法放松 我的主人失踪了
I will not take it easy, because I'm missing my person.
放松点伙计 像这样 转头 然后拉
Hey buddy, relax. Like this, turn and pull. Turn and pull.
别在意 你一会就会出来的
Forget about it, you'll be out no time.
这都是什么东西 它们减弱了我的能力
What are these things? They're weaken me.
- 泡沫塑料包装粒 - 泡沫塑料?
- Polystyrofoam packing peanuts. - Styrofoam?
肯定是绿眼人谋划的!
This is a "green-eyed man" written all of it!
你们有没有见到一个绿眼睛的人?
Have you seen a man with a green eye?
我得说两句 要是可以的话
You know, I gotta say something, if I could say something here.
你很眼熟啊 乔伊 看看他的脸
You look familiar. Joey, look at this guy's mug.
是啊 我发誓 我以前见过他的
Yeah, you know, I could've sworn I've seen this guy before.
对 对 对
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我可跟你说 我过目不忘的
I gotta tell ya, I never forget a face.
- 他从来不忘 - 是啊
- He never does. - Oh, yeah, yeah.
- 从不 - 是 他很擅长记人相貌
- Never. - Yeah, he's really good with the faces and such.
听着 我要找绿眼人 你们都知道些什么 小鸟!
Listen, listen! The man with the green eye. Tell me what you know, birds!
- 我认识这狗 - 对啊 我也是
- I know this dog. - Yeah, yeah, me too!
我明明记得的 这可要了命 等一下
I gotta remember, it's gonna kill me. Hold on.
不 我还是想不起来 我以为我知道的
No, I don't know. I, I, I thought I know.
你没有和一个叫开尔文的流浪狗 一起在第14大街闲逛?
Hey, you ever hang out down on 14th Street with a stray named Kelvin?
- 对 对 对 开尔文 拉布拉多狗 - 什么?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Kelvin, the Labrador. - What?
你得告诉我点什么 这实在是太"欢谬"了
You gotta gimme something here, cause this is redonkulous.
绝对完全的"欢谬"!
Absolutely redonkulous!
最最"欢谬"! 你知道那什么意思么?
Capisch redonkulous! Ya know what that means?
你们这些鸽子真没用
You pigeons are useless.
我需要有 绿眼人身边的人
I need someone on the inside, someone close to the green-eyed man.
- 一只猫 - 哦 找一只猫?
- A cat. - Oh, a cat?
是的 一只猫 一旦找到他...
Yeah, a cat. When I find him...
一旦我找到他 就会让他生不如死
When I find him, I'm gonna make that cat wish never born.
我想我们认得你说的猫
I think we know just the cat.
很准时 索尔 进来吧
Right on time, Saul. Come on in.
好 索尔 干得不错 下次给我找点芥末 好吧 ?
Okay, Saul, nice work. Let's find some mustard next time. Okay, babe?
好的 米滕 谢谢你 米滕
Yes, Mittens. Thank you, Mittens.
这是你弄来的全部么 特德?
Is that everything you've pickled, Ted?
- 好孩子! - 再见 米滕
- What a boy! - Good day, Mittens.
路易!
Louie!
这是什么?
What is this?
这星期不景气 这可是我一半的家当
It was a slow week. I mean, that's half of what I got.
你听到了么 路易 我都快饿死了
You hear this, Louie? I'm starving here.
要是我的胃开始说话 它就不是跟我说了
And when the old stomach starts talking, it's not talking to me.
- 而是跟我的爪子说 - 别举爪子 求求你!
- It's talking to... the claws! - Not the claws! Please!
我在努力控制这些坏家伙 但事情也不是全取决于我
I'm holding these bad boys back as best as I can, but the thing is it's not up to me.
胃和爪子之间有一条直线...
The stomach got a direct line to these babies,...
而且都在对我喋喋不休呢
...and I'm picking up a lot of chatter!
要我和爪子谈的话 作为交换
So, I'll talk to the claws, but in exchange...
- 下周 你要交出所有的食物 - 可是我们有约在先的!
...next week, all your food comes to me. - But that's not our deal!
我给你一半 你保护我 我们说好的
I bring you half, you give me protection! That's our deal.
那好吧 这个协议已经过期了 现在给我消失
Yeah, well, the deal just expired. Now, get lost.
记住我的话 米滕
Mark my words, Mittens.
总有一天 会有人教训你的!
One day, someone's gonna stand up to you! Someone's gonna teach you a lesson!
是么 我都要害怕死了
Yeah, I'm really scared now.
你是该害怕!
You should be!
哦 好的 你...
Aaah! Okay! You...
她在哪?
Where is she?
- 谁? - 你知道我干嘛来的!
- Who? - You know why I'm here!
她在哪?
Where is she?
好吧 伙计 我不知道你在找什么...
Okay, okay! Look buddy, I don't know what you're getting at, but...
说吧 米滕 告诉这家伙她在哪
Come on, Mittens. Just tell the guy where she is.
- 告诉这小狗 别惹他不高兴 - 对啊 说吧 告诉他
- Tell the dog, make him happy. - Yeah, yeah, come on, Mittens! Tell him!
乔伊 文尼 鲍比 我的好孩子!
Joey, Vinnie, Bobby, my boys!
你们干嘛不告诉这疯狗 他找错了猫?
Would you tell the crazy canine that he's got the wrong cat?
- 你找到她了 伙计! - 就是她!
- You got her, pal! - That's her!
- 就是你要找的那只猫! - 绝对是!
- She's the one! - That is definitely the right cat!
看来非得用狠招了
Looks like we're gonna do this the hard way.
喔 啊 你疯了 哥们
Whoa! Aaah! You're crazy, man!
乔伊 我们是不是有点过分了?
Hey Joey, do we go too far on this?
开什么玩笑 这是我生命中最好的一天
You kidding? This is the best day in my life.
你为本和巴特工作 他们是绿眼人的手下
You work for Ben and Bart, who work with the man green-eye.
他们带走了Penny 她现在在哪?
They take him Penny. Where is she?
- 我不知道你在说什么 - 这让人有点累了...
- I don't know what you're talking about. - This is becoming tiring so cat...
事实上 我正想打一个哈欠
...in fact, I feel a yawn coming on.
好吧 好吧 我说 我全说 我知道Penny在哪
Okay, okay, I'll talk, I'll talk. I know where Penny is.
没错 他们抓住了她
Yeah, they have her.
那个蓝眼睛的黑衣人
Yes, the men in black and the guy, the guy with the blue eyes.
蓝眼睛?
Blue eyes?
哦 绿眼睛 那个绿眼睛的人
Oh, green! Yes, green! The one green eye.
你还在撒谎 天生的谎言家 真让人讨厌
You just can't stop lying, can you cat? It's in the genes. This is gross.
我知道 这很讨厌 我也讨厌我自己
I know, it's disgusting, I disgust myself.
好莱坞?
Hollywood?
你放我下来 我就告诉你她在哪
But if you put me down, I'll show you where she is.
松饼之家
瞧 你得明白 我这可是冒风险的
You know, I hope you appreciate the risk I'm taking here.
我邪恶身体的每一根骨头 都在告诉我
Every bone in my evil cat body is telling me...
不要背叛绿眼人
...not to betray the trust of the green-eyed man.
好了 这是全世界
Okay, this is a top, top secret map...
最最机密的地图!
...of the entire earth!
现在 我们是在这里 举着大火炬的绿女士旁边
Now, we're over here, by the green lady with the big torch.
而我的老板把Penny关在...
And my boss has Penny locked up...
就在...就在这里 这个戴太阳镜的饼干这里!
Right, right over... Here, here! By the waffle with the sun glasses!
你现在只需要从这里去到那里
Now all you need to do is get from here to there.
好了 我告诉你去哪找他 你放开我 我马上闪人
Well, I told you where you find her, so if you'll just untie me, I'll be on my way.
找到Penny就放了你
I'll release you cat, when we found Penny.
什么 不是这样的 我们有约在先的
Excuse me? That wasn't the deal! We had a deal!
你的协议刚刚过期
Your deal just expired.
十分钟前 她也是这么跟我说的
She said that to me, not 10 minutes ago.
真讽刺!
The irony!
太好了
Perfect.
嗯 锁上了
Hmm... padlock.
听着 疯狗(Cujo电影名 又名凶狗古卓) 我的手掌下面藏着邪恶的利爪...
Listen Cujo, I got some pretty wicked claws under these mitts,...
别逼我把它们亮出来!
...do not, I beg of you do not make me bring out these bad boys!
会很吓人的!
It gets ugly!
- 你在干什么? - 待在后面!
- What are you doing? - Stay back!
要是我用力凝视这把锁 它就会着火然后熔化的
If I stare at the lock really hard, it'll burst into flames and melt.
现在我越来越担心了
Now I'm concerned on a number of levels.
- 轻点 看着路 - 我很好 还是往前走吧
- Easy, watch! Watch it those! - I'm good. We gotta go.
有人来了!
Intruders!
嘿 慢一点 你这疯狗...
Hey! Slow down you screwy borrowed of mind...
- 哦 哥们 这东西很重 - 嘿嘿 先放下来
- Oh, boy, this thing is heavy. - Hey, hey! Put it down.
我把钥匙拉下了
I forgot the keys.
我就回来
I'll be right back.
嘿 幸运硬币
Hey, lucky Penny.
谢了 起来干活儿吧
Thanks. Now move your butt.
好了 往左面抬 我抬不... 不 我能抬住
Okay, just upon your left. Yeah. I got... No, I got, I got mine.
好了么?
You got it?
话都快到嘴边了 我认识那狗
It's on tipping my tongue. I know that dog.
我跟你们说 乔伊 鲍比 我好像是... 我跟你们说
I'm telling you, Joey. Bobby, you guys looking at me like, you don't know. I'm telling you...
我认得这狗 我在哪见过他
...I know this dog. I've seen him somewhere.
你今晚就会想起来的 等你飞落后
You remember it tonight, when you're perching.
好的 是...这么回事
Allright, that's... That's will happen.
- 我有些好消息! - 真的么?
- I've got some good news! - Really?
是的 我刚安排你当 今晚节目的主要嘉宾!
Yes, I do. I just booked you, on the tonight show's "main guest"!
那很好 我是说...
That's right. That, I mean...
要是Bolt还没找到 这又有什么意思
...which means just absolutely nothing, if Bolt is still missing.
这连不算是个好消息 上今晚的节目 我才稀罕
It's not even a good news, like whatever, so up tonight show. Who cares? I don't care.
没事的 宝贝
It's okay, baby.
- 他一定很害怕 - 害怕? 他是Bolt啊
- He must be so scared. - Scared? This is Bolt we're talking about.
他从不害怕
He's not scared of anything.
我猜Bolt希望你上今晚的节目
I bet Bolt would want you to the tonight show.
这...
It is...
或许不是
I just... or maybe not.
Bolt非常爱你 你在这里
Bolt loves you very much sweety. And you're here.
他不会走远的
He couldn't have gone far.
欢迎来到俄亥俄州 期待您的发现!
Welcome to Ohio. So much to Discover!
要是你有超能力的话 我想这会让你...
So, if you got super powers, I guess that would make you, what...
成为超狗什么的? - 这是机密消息
...like some kind a super dog? - That information is classified.
哦 说说嘛 你最强的能力是什么?
Oh, come on! Like, what's your best power?
你移动快么 还有飞呢 你能飞么?
You go to move. How about flying? Can you fly?
别傻了 我不能飞
Don't be silly, I can't fly.
好吧 要是你没有任何能力的话...
Okay, okay, fine. If you don't have any powers,...
你有没有超能力 和我有什么相干?
...you don't have any powers. What's it to me?
- 我会狮子吼 - 超级狗叫吗? 喔 开什么玩笑?
- I have super bark. - A super bark? Wow, you're kidding me?
这个狮子吼到底有什么用?
What exactly this one do with the super bark?
我真的不能告诉你 那是机密
I really can't talk about it. It's classified.
我建议你别再问了 带我去见Penny
I suggest you pipe down and take me to Penny.
看来你和这个Penny 彼此分不开咯 小子?
You're awfully attached to this Penny character, huh wags?
- 她是我的主人 - 拜托 她只是个人而已
- She is my person. - Oh, please. She's a person.
如果你问我的话 唯一的好人是...
And if you ask me, the only good person is a...
泡沫塑料!
Styrofoam!
跟紧了!翻滚!
Tag and roll!
跟紧了 然后什么?
Tag and what?
这是? 我爪子里流出来的 红色液体是什么?
What? What is this red liquid coming from my paw?
那是血 大英雄!
It's called blood, hero!
-我需要它么? -是的
- Do I need it? - Yes.
要是你不想让它流光的话...
So if you want it to keep inside your body where it belongs,...
...你就不该再从高速路 的飞车上纵身跳下!
...you should stop jumping off trucks doing eighty on the interstate!
是啊...通常我是刀枪不入的 一定是因为...
Yeah, well, normally I'm attain more indestructible. Must have been the...
泡沫塑料! 是那东西使我变弱的!
Styrofoam! That stuff, it weakens me!
- 你在干吗?把它放下! - 好吧 我已经受够你了
- What are you doing? Put that down! - Allright, that's it. I've had with you.
小狗 为我松绑 不然... 我就会给你点颜色瞧瞧!
Untie me, pooch or I'm gonna... I'm gonna... Uhmm... I'm gonna seriously wound you!
我会用这个泡沫塑料来教训你!
I'm gonna seriously wound you with this styrofoam!
你疯了么?你难道不知道 泡沫塑料的威力么!
Are you mad? You don't know the power of styrofoam!
哦 你说对了 小宝贝 我现在要释放它了!
Oh, you bet on that, baby. And I'm about to unleash it!
- 泡沫塑料的威力! - 不要!
- The power of the styrofoam! - No!
好吧 猫咪 好吧 你赢了 我会为你松绑的
Alright, cat. Okay, you win. I'll untie you.
能让那架钢琴飞起来的 一定是种奇异的力量!
That's a weird push to put a piano!
- 我们之间还会有什么问题吗 小猫? - 不不不  没有了
- Are we gonna have any more problems, cat? - No, no, no. No more problems.
我带你去见Penny
I'll take you to Penny.
噢!那是什么?
Ah! What is that?
- 什么? - 就是这个!
- What? - That!
好吧  给你2秒钟告诉我 下了什么毒 猫!
Okay, you have two seconds to tell me what you've implanted in me, cat!
毒药?寄生虫?毒药? 等等 这个我说过了 是吧?
Poison? A parasite? Poison? Wait, I just said that, didn't I?
你看 我已经糊涂了! 我不能思考了!
See, I'm all discombobulated! I can't think straight!
噢 不是吧  你肚子饿了!
Oh, I don't believe this. You're hungry!
- 解药在哪? - 行啦 行啦!好吧!
- Where is the antidote? - Okay, okay! Alright!
那就是你的解药...
There's your antidote...
食物!
Food!
好吧!谁想吃汉堡?
Alright! Who wants burgers?
看看这个!
Watch this!
去吧 用狗脸 一定有效
Go on, use the dog face. This gonna be beatiful.
也就是哀求 装个可怜狗狗的表情!
You know, beg. Do the dog face!
什么? 狗脸? 那是什么意思?
What? The dog face? What is that mean?
我认识了世界上唯一一条 不晓得装可怜的狗
Taking same tie to the one dog on earth, he doesn't know how to beg.
好吧 如果你想要食物...
Okay. If you want the food...
...想要解药 你就要完全按我说得办
...the antidote, you're gonna have to do exactly what I say.
不 不可能 你是堕落的黑暗生物
No, not likely. You're a degenerate creature of darkness.
是啊 是啊 就算是吧
Yeah, yeah, granted but that's it.
我要你做的只是 稍微倾斜一下你的头
All I'm asking you to do is just tilt your head a little.
你能做到的是么? 快点
You could do that, can't you? Come on.
- 再斜一点 多斜一点... - 这太傻啦
- More, more... - This is stupid.
不 不 加把劲 再努力下 拜托啦 你就快做到了
No, no. Come on. Work with on this. Please, you're almost there.
哦 天哪!
Oh, boy!
好吧 试试另外一边
Okay, try the other way.
就这样啦!头高一点!低一点 现在再来点笑容 放松
There you go! Head up! Down. Now, a little smile. Loose the smile.
左耳放下来 另外一只 好吧 那样更加好一点
Drop your left ear. Your other left. Okay, the other way was better.
现在 两个耳朵都放下去 保持这个姿势 就这样
Now, drop them both. Hold it, right there.
然后再往上方看一点点
And ever so slightly, look up.
大餐来啦 宝贝!
Soup is on, baby!
给你
Here you go.
对啦!
Yes!
哦 看看你 小家伙!
Oh, look at you, you little guy!
给你 蠢猫!
Here you stupid cat!
...到底发生了什么? 你怎么啦?
...what really happened. And what is that matter to you?
- 我恋爱啦 - 和有钱佬?
- Because I'm involved. - With rich?
- 和詹姆斯 - 如果你和詹姆斯在一起的话...
- With James. - If you and James are romantic...
- ...我要知道全部经过 - 什么?你是不是...
...I wanna know all about it. - What? Are you...
真是晴天霹雳!
Come undone!
如果你阻止了泄露 你就可以得到奖赏!
You gonna get something if you'll stop that leaking!
跑啊 拉瑞 快跑 停!
Go Larry, go Larry, go Larry! Stop!
我们只做过一次 那次真是太糟糕了
We did only once. It was a disaster.
它真的很有用 能帮助释放血清素且...
It really does help and it really releases the serotonin and...
嘿 老兄!这次按我的 方法处理这件事!
Hey, man! This time we'll do it my way!
你好小狗 想不想尝尝 奶奶做的黄油豆子饺子?
Well, hello puppy. Did you come for some of grandma's butter bean dumplings?
在这儿等会儿哦
You wait right there.
瞧你 你真是天才演员 哈?
Look at you. You're quite a little actor, huh?
我很久没吃过这样好了
I haven't eating like this in ages.
你看! 我的肚子鼓出来啦 太棒啦!
Hey, look! My stomach distended. How great is that!
是啊 别高兴太早了 我们还得继续赶路
Yeah, well. Don't get used to it. We gotta keep moving.
但这是宝地啊 你傻了吗?
But this place is a gold mine. What's wrong with you?
每周都有新的旅游者 为我们提供新的食物
Every week, new RVs bring us, new suckers who bring us new food.
你看看吧! 真是完美啊!
Look around! It's perfect.
难道是我的眼睛在骗我? 难道这是幻觉么?
In my eyes deceive me? Is this some apparition I see before real?
哦 这是真的么? 我的英雄!
Oh, could it be? My hero!
哦 天哪! 哦 天哪!
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
你是闪电狗 那只超狗! 你太帅啦!
You're Bolt, the super dog. You're fully awesome.
等下 你认识这只狗吗?
Wait a minute. You know this dog?
- 是的 他实在是太棒啦! - 是的 这个我已知道了
- Oh, I do. He is fully awesome! - Ah, yeah, yeah. We've established that.
- 你是谁? - 我是Rhino(犀牛)
- Who are you? - I'm Rhino.
一只叫犀牛的仓鼠?
Rhino, the hamster?
我的祖先不全是仓鼠 我有十六分之一狼的血统...
Well, you know, my ancestry isn't all hamster. I'm 1,16% wolf...
...以及黄狼獾 还有一些...
...with a yellow wolverine and there is some between...
不过先不说这个!
But that besides the point!
现在我和我的英雄在一起 闪电狗 那只超狗!
We have for us a legend. Bolt, the super dog!
他跑得快过导弹 他的激光视线能烧穿金属
You can outrun speeding missiles, and burn through solid metal with his heat vision.
最厉害的是 他的狮子吼 能摧毁一切建筑!
And best of all, he can obliterate large structures with his super bark!
等等 你见过狮子吼?
Wait a minute, you've seen the super bark?
- 你是不是一直在监视我? - 是啊 我一直在关注你呢
- Have you been observing me? - Oh, yeah. I watch you all the time.
- 这不可能啊 - 哦 其实没什么的啦 真的
- That's incredible. - Oh, it's nothing, really.
但是我一直非常警觉! 没人能逃过我的眼睛!
But I'm always so vigilant! No one can avoid my detection!
- 你是一个幽灵 - 如果你非要这么想的话...
- You are a phantom. - Ah, if you say so...
哦 嘿!看着哦!
Oh, hey! Check it out!
再想一想这个英勇的姿势 怕了吧 是吧?
Think again this bold action. Scary, huh?
- 就好像 我们是双胞胎 - 是啊 好吓人
- It's like, we're twins. - Yeah, scary.
- 那么...Penny在哪儿? - 她被绿眼人绑架了
- So, where is Penny? - She was kidnapped by the green-eyed man.
绑架?太可怕了! 她也许已经命丧黄...
Kidnapped? This is terrible! She could be in grave...
...岌岌可危 我知道 但我抓住了这只猫
Grave danger. I know. But I've captured this cat.
我猜她是绿眼人的奸细!
An agent of the green-eyed man, I presume!
你猜的没错 她正要带我去找Penny
You presumed correctly. She is taking me to Penny.
你! 你真是一个 十恶不赦的坏蛋
You! You are a vile vermin.
你晚上怎么睡得着? Penny是世界上最最好的人
How did you sleep at night? Penny is the most wonderful person ever.
她喜欢闪电狗 闪电狗棒极了 你却是如此邪恶!
She loves Bolt and he is awesome. And you're a monster!
你怎么敢用你的邪恶来破坏 他们的关系!
How dare you destruct their relationship with your evil!
- 去死吧!去死吧! - 噢!噢!
- Die! Die! - Ow! Ow!
让我来把她灭掉 闪电狗
I can take her Bolty.
- 去死吧!去死吧! - 别激动 别激动 犀牛
- Die! Die! - Easy, easy, Rhino. Easy.
你是对的 我们需要她活着
You're right, we need her alive.
我们?
We?
是的 Bolt 我可以帮你
Yes. Bolt, I can be a valuable addition to your team.
- 你继续说 - 我如闪电般神速
- I'm listening. - I'm lightning quick.
我的反应能力如刀刃般尖锐 而且我擅长秘密行动
I have razor sharp reflexes and I'm a master of stealth.
我会让这只猫老实点的
Plus, I'll keep the cat in check.
- 前途多险阻 - 我有的是胆量(Ball和球同音)
- The road would be rough. - I have a ball.
- 没有回头路可走 - 我会极力向前行
- There is no turning back. - I guess I have to roll with the punches.
- 我们必须彼此信任 - 我保证
- Easy will be parley equation. - Promise.
我必须提醒你 前路危险重重
Gotta warn you, going into the belly of the beast, danger in every turn.
- 我把危险当早餐 - 你现在饿了吗?
- I eat danger for breakfast. - You're hungry?
- 我简直要饿死啦 - 那么欢迎加入我们
- Starving. - Welcome aboard.
嘿 我们能谈一谈么?
Hey, can we talk for a second?
我不懂这是咋回事 我只想知道...
I don't know what's going on here but I'm just a little bit concerned...
...这一路上还会 遇上多少神经病
...about the numbers of lunatics on this trip.
- 我的极限是一个 - 他和我们一起去
- My limit is one. - He is coming with us.
但我...
But I...
快走 犯人! 天马上就要黑啦
Move it prisoner, we're losing daylight.
说得对
I agree.
现在 我们需要找到 最好的交通工具
Now, we need to find the best set of wheels.
我有一个好主意 跟我来!
I've got a better idea. Follow me!
好吧 我们要做的 就是迅速跃到目标上
Okay. So we do here is we get the target with a quick fly over.
只要做一个抛物线运动 还有什么要补充的吗 犀牛?
We just the trajectory in the land dead center. Am I missing anything, Rhino?
和你在一起的 每一分钟都会变成...
Just the knowledge that every minute spent in your company becomes...
...我生命里最美好的时光!
...the new greatest minute of my life!
不 不要! 你们这俩疯子 我才不跳呢
No, forget it! How do you say, "No way I'm doing this" in crazy?
- 镇定 小猫 我罩着你呢 - 那才令人担心呢
- Calm down, cat. You're with me. - That's the problem.
你能不能放松一点?
Oh, would you be relax?
每次在"魔盒"里看你这么做 我都觉得超帅!
Every time you get this on the "magic box", it was awesome!
魔啥?
Magic what?
就是人们都盯着看的"魔盒"
You know, "magic box", people stare at.
等等! 是不是那个 有会动画面的魔盒?
Wait a minute! Is this the magic box that moving pictures on it?
是的 闪电狗的画面是最棒的
Yeah and Bolt's pictures are the best.
闪电狗的画面? 当然咯! 他以前是一个...
Bolt's pictures? Of course! He's a former...
不 等等 等等! Bolt 同志们! 听我说!
Oh, no! Oh, no! No, wait, wait! Bolt, guys! Hear me out!
- 我们走吧! 跳啊! 跳! - 等等 你不是一个超级英...
- Let it begin! Let it begin! Let it begin! - Wait, you're not a super he...
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
Mittens!
Mittens 抓住我的爪子 我不想要你死
Mittens, take my paw. I need you alive.
是啊 那就离我远点!
Yeah, of course! Stay away from me!
- 抓住我的爪子 我会救你的! - 不 你不是真正的...
- Squeeze my paw, I'll save you! - No, you won't. You're not really a...
Bolt!
坏蛋!
Saboteur!
好痛! 你这个白痴!
Ah! Ouch! You moron!
- 住嘴!我正在帮他 - 帮他? 是啊 没错
- Stop it! I'm trying to help him. - Help him? Yeah, right.
不要担心 Bolt! 我会搞定她的
Don't worry Bolt! I'll stop her.
我坚持不下去了
I can't hold it.
- 放开 你这妖孽! - Bolt!
- Let it go, you monster! - Bolt!
The real world hurts, doesn't it? But you wouldn't know about that, would you?
现实世界里你会很痛 是吧? 这疼痛你以前没感受过 是吧?
下来 小猫 我们没有时间吵架
Get down here cat. We don't have time for this.
我去拿个梯子
I'll get a ladder.
Look, genius. You're a part of a TV show.
你知道吗 天才 你是电视节目的演员
你知道吗?电视机 那是人用来娱乐的工具
You know what that is? Television. It's an entertainment for people.
那是假的! 你想的都是假的!
It's fake! Nothing you think is real as real!
胡说八道!
That's has preposterous!
Bolt 你想一想 你走失之后 你的超能力都失效了 不是么?
Think about it Bolt. Since you got lost, none of your powers are working, aren't they?
你变得会流血了 会感到饥饿了 我说...
你还以为你天生就具有 超能力 和一个闪电纹身吗?
那是我力量的象征 小猫
那是化妆师弄上去的 小狗
太可笑了! 下来!
Get down here!
绝不
No.
Mittens 你再不听话 我就用狮子吼轰你下来
Mittens, so help me, I will super bark you out of that tree.
是啊 疯狗 试试你就知道了
Yeah, gone nuts. Let's see how that works out for you.
你让我别无选择
You leave me no choice.
哦 狮子吼哦 好怕哦 好怕哦!
Oh, the super bark. Scary, scary!
是啊 那真是太厉害了!
Yeah, that's really really super.
不是真的 不可能的
It's not true. This is not true.
我没有感到很"超级"嘛...
Wow! I don't feel really "super".
等等! 不 还是没有
Wait! No, it didn't.
好了好了 我知道了 你可以停了
Okay, okay. I get the idea, you can stop now.
够啦! 我说 小狗 别叫了!
That's enough! Seriously dog, stop! I'm not kidding.
你能不能不要叫了?
Would you stop?
好吧 好好 你是超级狗 闪电狗 安静 求你啦
Okay, fine. You're the super dog. Bolt, be quiet, please.
Bolt 我们快跑吧!
Bolt, we gotta run!
- Bolt! - 过来
- Bolt! - Come here.
动物管理员
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER
寻狗- 闪电狗
LOST DOG - BOLT
皮毛为白色 身体一侧有闪电标记 重谢! 请帮我找回我的好朋友
He is white with a lightning bolt on his side. REWARD! Please help me get my friend back.
看看这是谁 小姑娘! 是Bolt!
Look who we found young lady! It's Bolt!
- 他们找到它了! - Bolt!
- They found him! - Bolt!
这是不是你的那只小狗呢?
Isn't that right you little puppy dog?
这不是Bolt
That is not Bolt.
呃 那取决于你怎么看它了
Well, that depands on how you look at it.
在我小时候 我想要 一辆自行车做生日礼物...
You know, when I was little, I want a bicycle for my birthday...
...但是我的父母给了 我一个棒球手套 所以...
...but my parents got me a baseball glove. So...
你知道我是怎么做的吗? 我就当那手套是自行车
You know what I did? I pretended that baseball glove was a bicycle.
我每天都骑着它去学校
And I rode it to school every day.
是真实的故事哦
True story.
- 那不是他 - 我觉得是 真的
- It's not him. - I think it's him. I do.
谢谢
Thank you.
小朋友 我们开门见山吧
Look kid, it's time we are honest with you.
如果我们不恢复拍摄 就会有很多人失业
If we don't get back in the production, people are gonna lose their jobs.
- 他们都是好人 - 可Bolt还没回来
- Good people with families. - But Bolt is still out there.
- 我... - 我知道 我们知道你的感受
- And I... - I know, we feel for you.
现在你该长大了
And the last thing we wanna do is ask a little girl to make a grown up decision.
事已成定局 你不该在深陷其中了
But it's come to that, we need you to move on.
我们要你忘了Bolt
We need you to let Bolt go.
都是泡沫塑料惹的祸!
It must be made of styrofoam!
不 不! 不能这样就完了!
No, no! No, no, no! Please, it can't end like this!
小猫 别担心啦 我来想办法
Stop worrying cat. I'll get us out of here.
你不行的 Bolt 你什么都不行
You can't, Bolt. You got nothing.
你没有超能力 也没有狮子吼
No super strength, no super bark.
也没有激光视线
And no heat vision.
听我说好不好? 我们正被带到一个地方...
Listen to me, okay? We've been taking to a place...
...人们去那里挑选宠物 明白么?
...where humans go animal shopping, alright?
人们总是选那些可爱的
And this is what humans do. They always pick the cute ones.
那些长得和你差不多的 Bolt
The ones that look like you, Bolt.
而像我们这种就老死在里面了
But the rest of us never come back out.
我说了 我会想出办法的 明白么?
I said, I'll get us out of here, alright?
我的英雄!
My hero!
叮铃铃 叮铃铃 你是谁? 是命运!
Ring, ring. Who is it? Destiny!
我一直在等你的电话
I've been expecting your call.
哦 你还没有放弃么? 你会把脑浆撞出来的
Oh, you didn't given up already? You'll liquefy whatever brains you have left.
任何容器都限制不了我!
I can not be contained in any container.
你这个逃兵!看看这个!
You quitter! Watch this!
我做到了! 我又厉害了!
I did it! I'm back!
那个泡沫塑料真是个邪恶的东西
That styrofoam is a wicked stuff.
简直太帅啦!任何卡车都 关不住Bolt和犀牛!
Totally awesome! There is no truck that I know that can keep Bolt and Rhino!
犀牛 你怎么会在这里?
Rhino, what are you doing here?
哦 没什么 那时我正在 尝试散步新方法...
Oh, nothing. I was enjoying a new thing stroll...
...然后我就把卡车上 笼子的门撞得当当响!
...and then I just pop the hatch on hack the containment unit!
- 你...你开了门? - 是的 是我开的
- You... You open the door? - Yes, I did.
那...那真是太棒了 犀牛
That's... That's great, Rhino.
是啊 那...那太棒了
Yeah, that's... That's really good.
好吧 我们现在去救犯人
Alright, let's go get the prisoner back.
我...我不行的
I... I can't do it.
你说什么?
What did you say?
- 我做不到 - 什么...你是谁?
- I can't. - What... Who are you?
犀牛 你太... 你只是有点...
Rhino, you're just... Just a little...
- 你是闪电狗 - 但是我不是...
- You are Bolt. - But I'm not...
是谁单枪匹马摧毁了 绿眼人的海底实验室?
Who single handedly destroyed the green-eyed man's under sea labs?
是我 但是...
Me, but...
那是谁使他机器人 奥运会计划死于襁褓?
And who foiled his plan to infiltrate the Olympics with nastic cyborgs?
- 是谁 是闪电狗啊!是谁呢? - 是我 但没有一次是...
- Who, Bolt, who? Who? - Me, but none of them...
是你!你能行的 Bolt 因为 在这个地球上...
You! You can, Bolt. Because, all over this planet...
...还有很多动物想做却做不到
...there are animals who feel like they can't.
就好像一个小仓鼠 他曾经在旅游车里生活
Like a little hamster, who once spend his days in a RV park.
他梦想着有一天也能 救一个小女孩 然后听她说:
Dreaming of the day when he too would save a little girl from danger and be told:
"你做到了! 犀牛! 是你救了我!"
"You did it! You did it, Rhino! You saved the day."
他们需要的是一个英雄 闪电狗!
They need a hero, Bolt!
那是一个不畏艰难 勇往直前的英雄
Someone, who never mind what the odds, will do what's right.
他们需要一个英雄来告诉他们 有时不可能的事情...
They need a hero to tell them that sometimes the impossible...
...是可以成为可能的 只要你很棒的话!
...can become possible, if you're awesome!
你有一点说得很对 犀牛
Well, you're right about one thing, Rhino.
Mittens 现在真的需要一个英雄
Mittens does need a hero.
我想我应该挺身而出
I guess I'll have to do.
你是多么谦虚啊! 那么现在 谁要去救那只猫?
Such modesty! Now, who is going to save that cat?
- 我 - 谁?告诉我谁?
- Me. - Who? Tell me who?
我
Me.
我去拿我的球
I'll get my ball.
橡树郡 动物收留所
ELMWOOD COUNTY ANIMAL SHELTER
就在哪儿
Over there.
就是那里了
There it is.
这次就和你闯入卡利科的 研发中心差不多 注意掩护!
This will be just like the time, you infiltrated Calico's R.D. cover base!
这和那个不完全一样 犀牛
It's not gonna be exactly like that, Rhino.
我们要做一些小小的变动
We gonna have to do things a little differently.
哦 秘密行动模式!
Oh, stealth mode!
领养小动物周
ADOPT A PET WEEK
- 晚安 伊斯特 - 晚安 罗伊德
- Good night, Ester. - Good night, Lloyd.
罗伊德?
Lloyd?
罗伊德 你再吓唬我 我就用喷雾剂对付你啦!
Lloyd Spoony, you jump out and scare me, and I'm gonna pepper spray again!
这真像和一个三岁小孩共事似的!
I swear it, it's like I work with toddlers!
威胁明确!
Threat not a doubt.
我感觉重获新生!
I feel alive!
有一个警卫
There's a guard.
我去扭断他的脖子
I'll snap his neck.
我们需要把他 从那个门边引开
We need to get away him from that door.
- 球! - 球?
- Ball! - Ball?
球! 球! 球! 球!
Ball! Ball! Ball! Ball!
哦 我...我在读... 我才开始...别吵啦!
Oh, come... I'm just... I'm read... I'm just... Oh, god! Just quiet down!
Mittens?
Bolt!
- 你在这干吗呀? - 我来救你出去
- What are you doing here? - I'm busting you out.
你来救我?
You came all the way back here, for me?
是啊
Yeah.
但你是怎么...我是说... 你没有超能力啊
But how did you... I mean... You don't have any super powers.
- 我知道 - 真的么?
- I know. - Really?
- 是啊 - 哇哦!
- Yeah. - Wow!
- 今天真是疯狂哈? - 是的 我经历了许多
- Crazy day for you, huh? - It's been a lot. Yes, it has.
- 你准备好了么? - 没有
- Are you ready for this? - No.
我也没
Me neither.
你们激动个什么?
Hey, hey, hey! What is twisting your giblets?
等等! 这仓鼠哪跑来的啊?
Hey, wait! Where did you get that hamster?
给我 给我
Give it, give it.
嘿 等等!
Hey, wait!
是开溜的时候啦!
Initiating escape!
罗伊德 把门堵住!把门堵住!
Lloyd, block the door! Block the door! Block the door! Block the door!
狮子吼! 狮子吼!
Super bark! Super bark!
天啊! 那可是我的新车!
Sweet Sister Francis! What did you do my new truck?
小心!
Hold that!
哦 天哪!好痛啊!
Oh, god! That's hurt!
- 你们俩都不想活了是吧! - 眼睛辣死啦!
- Both you boys need serious help! - Spicy eyes!
- 我们需要搭车 - 我已经弄到个大的啦
- We need a ride. - I got a big one.
别客气!
You're welcome!
我真不能相信! 我终于 亲眼看到了一回狮子吼
I can't believe it! My whole life, I wanted to see a real life super bark.
你就是传奇!
You are legendary!
Mittens...
如果...如果我不抓坏人 那么我是谁?
If... If I don't chase bad guys, than what am I?
我的意思是...我是...
I mean... What...
不要担心 做一只普通的小狗...
Don't worry about it. Being a regular dog,...
...是世界上最最开心的事情好不好?
...not like the greatest geek in the world, okay?
我告诉你一个秘密如何?
Look, I'm gonna let you in, on a little secret, okay?
别人都不知道的猫的秘密
Little known cat secret.
知道我们为什么讨厌狗们吗?
You know why we hate dogs?
因为我们想要变成狗啊 我们有恋狗情节
Because we wanna be dogs, we have dog complexes.
但是...狗们都做些什么呢?
But... But what are dogs do?
弄脏东西 睡觉 追自己的尾巴 咬鞋子
Slubber, sleep, chase tails, chew shoes.
这并不需要硕士学位
You don't exactly need a master's degree.
你知道 大多数狗都住在 一个像这样的地方
You know, most dogs living in a place like this.
...好吧 我不知道 他们做的事情有...
And uhm... Well, I don't know, they do things like...
住在这里? 可是...可是...
Out of this? But... But...
- 这是你的狗球 - 狗球是
- And this is your dog ball. - What is?
就是这个! 一整层! 一整层都是给狗住的!
This! The entire floor! It's the ground goes to the hound.
这是件多么酷的事情啊!
How cool is that?
在寒冷的夜晚 有这个再要一个线团团...
In the cold nights, this and a ball of yarn...
哦 没有比这个更好的事情了
Oh, doesn't give better than that.
你...你似乎对这个地方很熟悉
You... You seem to know a lot about this places.
是啊 我曾经在这样地方呆过 但你知道吗?我内心更像野猫
Yeah, I did my time in one of these, but I'm more be an alley cat heart, you know?
一有机会我立马行动 之后绝不回头
Sprung out first chance I got, never looked back.
犀牛很棒! 他是多么棒啊!
Rhino is awesome! He is so awesome!
他...他超越了帅 ...他超越了超级帅!
He is... He is beyond awesome. He... He is "be awesome"!
他...额!
He is... Uh!
我...我超级棒!
I... I am "be awesome".
现在告诉你什么是狗最想做的
I think it's about time I introduce you a regular dog peace to resistance.
- 把头伸出去 - 为什么?
- Get your head out. - Why?
照我说得做就行啦
Just do it.
这... 这真是太棒啦
This... This is awesome.
然后把你的舌头伸出来!
And stick your tongue out!
感觉棒极啦! 你为什么不试试呢?
This is totally awesome! Why don't you try it?
不用啦 谢谢 只有狗才这么干
No, thanks. It's really a dog thing.
# 我有很多可以给予
# I have got so much to give,
# 我发誓我有
# I swear I do.
# 也许我并没有九条命
# I may not have nine lives,
# 但是这次我感觉到了新生
# but this one feels brand new.
# 是的 我一直活得很快活
# Yes Ive lived a good one.
# 我试着过的真实
# I have tried to be true.
# 有些事情我从未想过
# There are some things I never realized,
# 直到我遇见你
# till I met you.
# 风儿吹拂脸颊的滋味
# How the wind feels on my cheeks,
# 对着月儿狂吠的感觉
# when Im barking at the moon.
# 你的家是如此独一无二
# There is no home like the one youve got,
# 因为那个家属于你
# cuz that home belongs to you.
# 我来啦
# Here I come
# 回到你身边
# back to you.
# 你的家是如此独一无二
# There is no home like the one youve got,
# 因为这个家属于你
# cuz that home belongs to you.
# 当我遇到困难的时候
# Well I was in trouble, bad.
# 我是如此困惑
# I was so confused.
# 亲爱的 我从没看到过彩虹
# I may not see in color babe,
# 我能感觉到只是忧郁
# but I sure can feel blue.
# 我经历了很多事
# I have been a lot of things,
# 也许他们不都是真的
# they may not all be true.
# 我的经历充满神秘
# My experience was so mysterious,
# 直到我遇见你
# till I met you.
# 也许现在旭日东升
# Now the sun may rise in the east,
# 但我正对着月亮狂吠
# but Im barking at the moon.
# 你的家是如此独一无二
# There is no home like the one youve got,
# 因为这个家属于你
# cuz that home belongs to you.
# 我来了
# Here I come
# 回到你身边
# back to you.
# 你的家是如此独一无二
# There is no home like the one youve got,
# 因为这个家属于你
# cuz that home belongs to you.
# 你的家是如此独一无二
# There is no home like the one youve got,
# 因为这个家属于你
# cuz that home belongs to you.
# 你的家是如此独一无二
# There is no home like the one youve got,
# 因为这个家属于你
# cuz that home belongs to you.
Bolt! 醒醒!
Hey Bolt, wake up.
快 我要给你个惊喜!
Come on, I've got a surprise for you.
好啦 好啦 不准偷看
Okay, okay, no picking.
好了 现在睁开眼睛吧
Alright. Now, open them.
这是世界上最好的地方 宝贝!
Best in the globe, baby!
让我来介绍一下好吧?
Just let me give you a grand tour, okay?
这个 这个是我的 这个 都是你的
This one, this one is mine. And this one is all yours.
- Mittens 我... - 哦 我把这个超级软枕头给你啦
- Mittens, I... - Oh, I found this really soft pillow thing for you.
知道吗?我找了些 泡沫塑料填在里面
And get this! I found some styrofoam and I stuffed it inside.
这样既有创意 又讽刺 你明白不?
Which I thought both kind of creative and ironic. You know what I mean?
- Mittens 我不认为... - 看这个!
- Mittens, I don't think that... - Check it out!
完全的隐私 百分百的隔音!
Total privacy and completely sound proof!
- 是啊  我不... - 好吧 我吹牛的 这不隔音
- Yeah, well, I don't think that I... - Okay, I lied. It's not sound proof.
- 但是 你知道... - Mittens 我不能呆在这里
- But, you know... - Mittens, I can't stay here.
- 什么? - 我离Penny还有一块饼干那么远
- What? - We're one waffle away from Penny.
你还想回去找她?
You still going back to her?
Mittens 她是我的主人
Mittens, she is my person.
我的耳朵 我的耳朵!
Ouch! Ouch! Ear, ear!
看着我 Bolt 我是真实的
Look at me, Bolt. I'm real.
现在 这个呢? 这是真实的吗?
Now, how about this, huh? Is that real?
你觉得这个很真实么? 那个呢? 那个是真的吗?
Is this look real to you? Or that? Is that real? Or that?
那个怎么样 Bolt? 她只是一个演员而已
How about that, Bolt? She is an actress.
- 她只是在演戏 - Penny才不是
- She is just pretending. - Not Penny.
世界上是没有Penny的 她是假的
There is no Penny. She is fake.
不对 你错了 她很喜欢我
No, you're wrong. She loves me.
不 不 Bolt 那是他们的工作 你懂吗?
No, no Bolt. That's what they do, okay?
他们表现得很喜欢你 表现得他们会永远陪你
They act like they love you. They act like they'll be there forever.
可是突然有一天 他们就收拾东西走人了...
And then one day, they pack up all their stuff and move away,...
...同时他们把对你的爱也带走了
...and take their love with them.
留下他们的猫自生自灭!
And leave their declawed cat behind to fend for herself!
他们抛弃了她...
They leave her...
...她却还在想她到底做错了什么
...wondering what she did wrong.
对不起Mittens 但是...
I'm sorry Mittens, but...
Penny不是这样的
Penny is different.
那就去吧
Then go.
- Mittens 我... - 你滚吧 Bolt!
- Mittens, I... - Get out of here, Bolt!
我一开始就不该可怜你
I never should take a pitty on you.
- 哦 Mittens... - 滚 Bolt!
- Oh, Mittens... - Just get out of here, Bolt!
你要照顾好自己
You take care of Mittens.
小心驾驶 出入平安
那块肉披萨 一点也不好吃!
That meat lover's pizza is not loving me back at all!
- 你好啊 犀牛 - 早安 猫咪
- Hey there, Rhino. - Morning, cat.
- Bolt呢? - 他...呃...
- Where is Bolt? - He is... Uh...
- 他走了 - Bolt走了?
- He's gone. - Bolt left?
是的 但是他...他要我告诉你.
Yeah, but he... Uhm... He instructed me to tell you, that he... Uhm...
他必须独自去面对绿眼人
He had to face the green-eyed man alone.
- 你去哪? - 去找他
- Where are you going? - To Bolt.
但他不再需要我们了
But he doesn't need us anymore.
相信我 我在电视里看过
Trust me, I've seen that a million times before.
在战斗开始前的黑夜里 当坏人的钢牙...
In the cold, dark night before the battle when the steely fangs of evil...
...磨得锋利 准备袭击的时候...
...are sharpened and points to strike...
...英雄必须独自去面对 他的最大的挑战
...the hero must go and face his greatest challenge alone.
但如果说闪电狗曾教会我什么的话...
But if Bolt's taught me anything,...
...那就是在他需要的时候 你绝不能丢下你的朋友!
...it's that you never abandon a friend in a time of need!
你的队友遇到困难 你就要挺身而出
When your team mates in trouble, you go.
不管他们是否向你求助 你都得去帮助他们!
Whether they ask or not, you go!
即使你不晓得 你是否还能活着回来...
Not knowing if you're coming back dead or alive...
他是朝另外一个方向去的
He went the other way.
...你得去帮助他们!即使 这要穷尽你毕生之力 也得去!
...you go! Knowing your deepest ravel it's gonna appears your eye, you go!
Penny!
不会吧! 哇哦! 闪电狗! 老兄 我可是你的忠实粉丝
No way! Wow! Bolt! I'm really a big fan of yours, brother.
我是布莱克 这是我的朋友汤姆 汤姆 打声招呼
I'm Blake. This is my friend, Tom. Tom, say what's up.
- 你好吗? - 哇!
- What's up? - Wow!
哦 不!
Oh, no!
这是我们的私人助理 比利...
And this is our personal assistant, Billy...
...他应该现在在电线上停着的
...who is supposed to wait up on the wire.
闪电狗 我已经仰慕你好久啦 有几句话我一直好想和你说...
Bolt, I've been admired you such a long time and there is something I always wanted...
...如果我有机会遇到你的话 现在我...
...to tell you if I ever get a chance to meet you. Now I...
好了 比利 你吓到人家了
Okay Billy, that was horrifying what you just did.
想要做些好事么?去拿些面包屑给我 要全谷物的 去吧!
Wanna make something useful? Go get me some bread crumbs. Whole grain. Go!
全谷物的 不是全麦的 比利!
Whole-wheat is not the same thing as whole grain, Billy!
- 不一样的 比利! - 不要拿全麦的回来!
- Not the same, Billy! - Do not come out with whole-wheat!
也不要黑面包 比利
Or pumpernickle Billy!
- 好吧 朋友们 我得走了 - 我知道 你一直很忙
- Okay guys, but I really gotta get going. - I know. I know you're a busy dog.
但你能不能抽几分钟听一下 我们对你节目的精彩策划...
But if you got a second for a lovely picture idea for your show,...
...汤姆比我会讲 由他来向你解释
...Tom has better pitching. I'll let him taking from here.
让我们把话筒交给汤姆
Tom has got the spotlight.
让我们拭目以待!
Wait for it!
- 外星人 - 很简单吧!
- Aliens. - Holy snap!
- 外星人? - 观众们喜欢外星人
- Aliens? - Audiences love aliens.
啊哈!
Holy crap!
- 他们应该是巨人 巨大的人! - 你碰不到我们的!
- It will be huge man! Huge! - You can't touch us!
挺好啊 其实我想问问你们 是否可以帮我找到Penny...
I love it. I'll tell you what, if you guys can help me find Penny,...
...就是那个电视里的女孩...
...the girl from the television show...
...我想进一步听听这个关于 外星人的点子 但是边走边说!
...I'd love hear more about this aliens idea, but on the way.
- 我们有希望啦! - 别激动!
- We got a nibble! - Don't freak out.
你这么搞砸"海底总动员"的
This is how you blew with Nemo.
我们以外太空的场景开始
We open exterior outer space scenery.
卡利科来抓Penny了
Calico comes for your Penny.
然后你就去揍扁他!
And then you squish him.
然后传输光束把你和Penny 带去外星人的母舰...
And as the tractor beam is pulling Penny and you to aliens' mother ship...
...画面渐暗
...we fade to black.
接着我们为片尾加上 首绝妙的流行歌
And we have a great pop song for the end credits.
和你的人谈一谈吧 我们策划的差不多了
Talk your people. We're ready to move on this.
看来有戏哦!
He is so on board!
就是这里啦!
There it is!
世界上最最恐怖的地方!
The most terrifying place on earth!
闪电狗 周四 晚八点
终于我们到达了虎穴
At long last, we've arrived at he belly of the beast.
这是绿眼人的老窝!
The lair of the green-eyed man!
犀牛 等等!
Rhino, hold up!
等等!
Hold up!
怎么 怎么啦? 我...难道我看上去不够帅?
What, what is the problem? I'm... I'm popped?
你听着 也许这对你来说 有点不可思议...
Listen, this may be really hard for you to understand...
...但 有时事情的真相很复杂...
...but you see, sometimes things aren't what they seem to be...
...有时你认为它是真的 但事实上却不是...
...and sometimes when you think something is really real and it's not,...
我等这一刻已经很久了
All of my training has prepared me for this moment.
去死吧!去死吧!
Die! Die!
准备去死吧 大走狗! 我要吃掉你的胰腺...
Prepare yourself, follow man beast! I will eat your pancreas...
...连同你的脾脏 我还要 把你的肝脏从你的身体里掏...
...with your spleen and then I will rip your liver out of your...
你长着小胡子 真可爱啊!
You're so cute with your little whiskers.
哦 在我很小的时候 我养了 一只和你一模一样的仓鼠
Oh, I had a hamster just like you when I was a kid.
Bolt!
Bolt! 你没事吧!
Bolt! You're okay!
你终于回来啦!
Oh, you came back!
Bolt 我以为再也见不到你了
Bolt, I thought I've lost you.
你真乖
You're my good boy.
乖
Good boy.
好啦 各位 我们去七号台 正式把这个演一遍
Okay, people. Let's move to stage 7 and do it for real.
- 我想他 - 我知道 宝贝
- I miss him. - I know, honey.
我也是
I do too.
请大家各就各位!
First positions, please!
好 亲爱的别动哦
Okay, hold still a little sweetie.
第十五场 第一幕 准备
15, take 1. Mark.
开拍!
And action.
啊 教授
Ah, Professor.
真该谢谢你...
I'd like to thank you for granting us an access...
...你那聪明的脑袋会协助我们
...to that labyrinthine mind of yours.
我是决不会这么做的
You know I'll never do such a thing.
这可事关你女儿的生死哦!
Unless it was only way to save your little girl's life!
- Penny! - 爸爸!
- Penny! - Daddy!
Bolt! 到这来 Bolt!
Bolt! Here, Bolt!
你的狗可不在这附...
Your dog is nowhere near...
抓住那只狗!
Get that dog!
去啊!去啊 去啊!
Go! Go, go!
没事的 宝贝 到这儿来!
It's okay, boy. Come here.
着火啦! 着火啦! 着火啦!
Fire! Fire! Fire! It's fire!
嘿 摇尾狗!
Hey Wags!
Mittens? 你在这干吗呀?
Mittens? What are you doing here?
说来话长 简单讲 我和 一只疯狗一起走遍全国...
Long story, short I was tied to a delusional dog and dragged across the country...
...但是那些都不重要 重要的是...
...but that is not important now. The real question is,...
...你在这里干吗? 你怎么不在里面?
...what are you doing here and why aren't you in there?
你说的对 Mittens
You were right about her, Mittens.
她...她不是真的
She, uh, well... it wasn't real.
不 Bolt 那是真的
No Bolt, it is real.
刚刚我在里面 看到她的表情
I was in there just now, I saw her face after you left.
她心都碎了
She's broken hearted.
她不要其他狗 她只喜欢你
She doesn't want just any dog, she loves you.
她是你的主人 Bolt 你是她的狗
She's your person, Bolt, and you are her dog.
- Bolt 你必须相信我 - Mittens 安静点!
- Bolt, you just gonna have to trust me on this. - Mittens, be quiet!
- 不 你必须听我说! - 不  我是认真的 安静点!
- No, you need to hear this! - No, no, seriously, be quiet!
怎么了?
What is it?
Penny!
- 救命! 救命啊! 救救我! - 再坚持一下!
- Help! Please, help! Help! - Hold on!
救救我!
Please!
哦 天哪! 舞台出事了!
Oh, my gosh! The stage!
是啊 你最好跑快点!
Yeah, you better run!
- 我会紧跟着你的! - 我们该做什么?
- I'm on your six. - What are we do?
我一定要进到那栋楼里面!
Just make sure I'll get inside that building!
Bolt?
- 里面还有人吗? - 我不知道
- Is anyone still in there? - I don't know.
快过去!
Coming through!
- 为了荣耀而死吧! - 我不会看着你死的 小龅牙!
- It's a good day to die! - Not on my watch, rodent!
Bolt!
我知道你会回来的
I knew you'll come back.
Bolt 急速移动!
Bolt, zoom zoom!
Bolt...
Bolt 你...你自己走吧
Bolt, just... just go on and out.
走吧
Go.
没事的
It'll be okay.
你是我的乖乖
You're my good boy.
我爱你
I love you.
你有看到我女儿吗? 有谁看到我的宝贝女儿了?
Have you seen my daughter? Has anyone seen my baby?
- 你听到了么? - 听到了
- Did you hear that? - Yeah.
安静! 大家请安静!
Quiet! Everyone be quiet!
那是狮子吼!
It's the super bark!
- 是从那面传出来的! - 我们走 走!
- It's coming from over there! - Let's go, go!
在这儿! 找到他们啦!
Over here! We found them! They're here! We found them!
请让一让!
Alright, we got a RG coming through people! Make it hole!
为了您的人生安全 请离开大楼
For your own safety, stay away from the building!
- Bolt - 亲爱的!
- Bolt. - Sweetie!
你不会有事的! 你不会有事的 你会好的!
You're okay! Oh, you gotta be okay. You're gonna be just fine.
- 她的情况稳定了 - 我们还是要带她去医院...
- She is stable. - We're gonna take her to the hospital...
...安全起见
...just to be safe.
对于发生的一切 我真的感到好难过
I'm so, so, so sorry does happened.
我难以想象你现在的感觉
I can't imagine, what you must feeling.
没有一个母亲应该承受 这样的痛苦 但是我...
No mother should ever have to go through something like this, but I...
...向你保证 我不会让 这一切白白浪费的
...promise you, we're going to make this work for us.
我是指封面故事 演出合约 电视制作商 执行编导...
I'm talking cover stories, production deals, executive producer credit...
这实在是太棒啦!
This is so great!
我们不干了!
We quit!
不 不 等等! 不要草率啊
No, no, wait! Let's not make any rush decisions.
我们再可以商量商量
Let's put a pin on it.
你受的伤...
I'm afraid your injuries far more severe...
...比我们预想的要严重 亲爱的
...then we've previously thought, my dear.
我们必须彻底给你整容
We have to completely reconstruct your face.
你看看
Have a look.
至少卡利科不会再认出我了
At least Calico won't be able to recognize me.
卡利科!
Calico!
Bolt!
什么?
What?
外星人!
Aliens!
这真是太离谱了
That is totally unrealistic.
- 百分百"欢谬" - 你说的没错
- Absolutely "redonkulous". - You could say that again.
对!就在那! 再过去一点!
Oh! Oh, yeah! Right there! Right there! Over!
是啊 就是这里
Yeah, that's the spot.
嘿 小笨狗!
Hey, silly doggy!
留个纪念!
That's a keeper.
你想要出去玩吗? 你想要出去玩么?
You wanna go play outside, huh? You wanna go play outside?
我们走吧!
Let's go!
- 那狗是不是看上去很眼熟? - 不是 我之前从没见过他
- Is that dog look familiar? - Nope. I've never seen him before in my life.
# 你的家是如此独一无二
# There is no home like the one you've got,
# 因为这个家属于你
# cuz that home belongs to you.